University of Arizona class records of students grades: submitted by instructors 1892-1915
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
University of Arizona class records of students’ grades: submitted by instructors,
1892-1915
AZ 052
University of Arizona
University of Arizona class records of students’ grades: Submitted by the instructors from 1892-1915.
2.0 linear ft.>
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Historical Note
Classes at the University of Arizona met for the first time in 1891 with 32 students but only six were admitted to the freshman class. The rest went to an established preparatory school because there were no high schools in the Arizona Territory. The University maintained separate preparatory classes for the first 23 years of operation. This archive contains class records from the University of Arizona for the years 1892-1915.
Arrangement
The Collection is arranged chronologically into 9 boxes by school year, and alphabetically by instructor's name.
Scope and Content Note
University of Arizona class records: Submitted by the instructors. The records include; the name of the class, student name, grade, year and semester: From 1892 through 1915.
Access Terms
University of Arizona -- Students.
University of Arizona -- History.
Preparatory school student -- United States.
Container List
- Class records: 1892-1893 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1894-1895 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1895-1896 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Class reocrds: 1896-1897 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1897-1898 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Class records: (I) 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Class records: (II) 1899-1899 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Class records: 1899-1900 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1900-1901 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1900-1901 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1901-1902 (A-F) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1902-1903 (G-H) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1902-1903 (I-Z) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Class records: 1903-1904 (A-F) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1903-1904 (G-R) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1903-1904 (S-Z) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1904-1905 (A-F) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1904-1905 (G-M) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1904-1905 (N-Z) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Class records: 1905-1906 (A-L) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1905-1906 (M-R) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1905-1906 (S-Z) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1906-1907 (A-G) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1906-1907 (H-Q) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1906-1907 (R-Z) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Class records: 1907-1908 (A-K) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1907-1908 (L-Q) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1907-1908 (R-Z) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1908-1909 (A-B) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1908-1909 (C-G) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1908-1909 (H-M) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1908-1909 (N-S) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1908-1909 (T-Z) (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1909-1910 (A-B) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1909-1910 (C-G) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1909-1910 (H-M) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1908-1910 (N-S) (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1909-1910 (T-Z) (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (A-B) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (C-E) (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (F-G) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (H-M) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (N-Q) (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (R-S) (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Class records: 1910-1911 (T-Z) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Class records: 1911-1912 (Very Incomplete B-S) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Class records: 1912-1913 (A-M) (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Class records: 1912-1913 (N-Z) (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Class records: 1913-1914 (A-K) (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Class records: 1913-1914 ((L-Z) (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Class records: 1914-1915 (A-K) (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Class records: 1914-1915 (L-Z) (Box 9, Folder 7)